[{"answer": "Na", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Suicide.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Do you realize this is the last meal I am going to have for three days?", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Come on, it's just down the hall", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Suicide.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I'll give you 50 cents", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Nah, I don't go for these no", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Suicide.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Hi", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "hey, you know what? I just remembered something. I had a dream about that guy last night. This is amazing", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Suicide.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I haven't seen him for months", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I'd love to go. Make an appointment", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Suicide.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I just got fired", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Psychics, vacations. How about getting a job", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Suicide.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Alright, come on, lets get out of here", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Who", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Suicide.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "He was screaming about it all night. How it's too sweet and it falls apart when you eat it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Suicide.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I wasn't", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I'm sorry if I caused any trouble. I was just being friendly", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Suicide.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "You weren't", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You know I don't get that whole suicide machine. There's no tall buildings where these people live? They can't wrap their lips around a revolver like a normal person", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Suicide.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Well, I went with her to the hospital last night", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Ah, what kind of a man are you? The guy is unconscious in a coma and you don't have the guts to kiss his girlfriend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Suicide.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "There is no coma etiquette. You see that's the beauty of the coma, man. It doesn't matter what you do around it", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I'd give him 24 hours to get out of it. They can't get out of it in 24 hours, it's a land rush", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Suicide.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "NOTHING LEFT! That's why I'm trying to get that vacuum cleaner. Because somebody's going to grab it.", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "It's disgusting", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Suicide.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Oh fine, I don't like to be around people who are just so irresponsible", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well, they're three kind of funny looking guys and they hit each other a lot", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Suicide.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I will show you The Stooges", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "He'll have a lot of catching up to do, I guess", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Suicide.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "How up to date", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I'll bring him up to date", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Suicide.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Oh, all the way up", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "my friend's Coffee Cak", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Suicide.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "From my house. I got a whole box of them", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "All right! All right. I won't say anything", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Suicide.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I swear", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I swear", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Suicide.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "On my mother's life", "qsentId": 38}]